grokdotcom.com 2011-06-16

# Privacy Policy of Future Now Inc and GrokDotCom

Questions? (877) 643-7244

We value your privacy! We will never give, lease, sell or otherwise disclose your personal information. Period! Any information you give to Future Now, Inc. at any of our sites (including: [ www.futurenowinc.com](http://www.futurenowinc.com/) or [www.grokdotcom.com](http://www.grokdotcom.com/)) will be held with the utmost care, and will not be used in ways to which you have not consented. A more detailed explanation about how we safeguard your personal information is described below. If you have any questions at all about our privacy policy, please [email us](mailto:privacyinfo@grokdotcom.com). 

**Resale or disclosure of information to third parties**

Future Now, Inc. does not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease any personal information collected at our site, including contact forms, download requests or email lists. 

**Browser information collected on the web site**

Future Now, Inc. analyzes the web site logs to improve the value of the materials available on the web site. 

**Privacy of our email lists**

Individuals must affirmatively ask to join our mailing lists using the forms provided on this web site or other means expressly sanctioned by Future Now, Inc. We do not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease the addresses on our list to anyone. In addition, we configure our list server software to refuse to divulge the email addresses of our list subscribers to anyone but authorized Future Now, Inc. staff, including other list subscribers. 

**Unsubscribe Policy  
**We strive to only send e-mail to those who want to receive it. If you would not like to receive future e-mails from us, reply to any email with **UNSUBSCRIBE** as the subject.

## Recent Clients

Hewlett-Packard  
Full Tilt Poker  
1-800-Flowers  
FatWallet  
Whistler.com  
Network Solutions  
CardScan  
NBC Universal  
Allegis  
WebEx  
ShoeLine  
ICE.com
